Ted, you bought
this painting?
Grandpa, this is
my girlfriend.
She's the one who brought it.
Oh.
Grandpa,
I'm so sorry.
It was
intended to be
your birthday gift,
but someone
thought it was fake
and tore it up.
No, it cannot be real.
No, I mean,
he may be the...
the Knights'
head coach, but
he can't afford
something like this.
It has to be a
fake, obviously.
I got it.
Ted must have
stolen team funds!
He's been lying
this whole time,
and now he says
that they grabbed it
from her collection?
Come on.
I'm calling the cops.
Allen,
the truth is right
in front of you.
You just refuse
to see it.
Sweetheart,
you're way too
gorgeous to waste
your time with
a crook like him.
Come with
me instead.
I can show you
the high life.
The high life?
Of course.
I'm the Knights'
security manager,
I mean, what are we
talking about here?
This guy,
just a criminal.
If you don't
want to end up
in prison with him,
you wanna be
on my side.
You know
what I mean?
How dare you
threaten her?
Do you even
know who she is?
Sure I do.
She's Ted's girlfriend.
Ted, don't worry.
Once you're
locked up,
I'm gonna take very
good care of her.
Well, I'm
not going to jail,
Allen.
Actually,
Grace,
owns the Knights.
What?